{
  "purchaseProperty": [
    {
    "question": "Player has the ability to purchase a property. What would you like to do?",
        "answers": [
          {
            "answer" : "Purchase a Property.",
            "value" : 0
          },
          {
            "answer" : "Do nothing / Burn the ability to purchase a property.",
            "value" : -2
          }
        ],
    "sub-questions" : [
      {
        "question": "Which property would you like to buy?",
        "answers": [
          "TO BE PROGRAMMATICALLY UPDATED"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
  ],
  "optionals" : [
    {
      "question": "Would you like to perform any optional actions?",
      "answers": [
        {
          "answer": "Trade with another player.",
          "value": 0
        },
        {
          "answer": "Build a pipeline.",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "answer": "None.",
          "value": -2
        }
      ],
      "sub-questions": [
        {
          "question": "What would you like to trade?",
          "answers": [
            "TO BE PROGRAMMATICALLY UPDATED"
          ],
          "sub-questions": []
        },
        {
          "question": "Where would you like to build a pipeline? ",
          "answers": [
            "TO BE PROGRAMMATICALLY UPDATED"
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "purchaseFirstProperty": [
    {
    "question": "Player has the ability to purchase a property. What would you like to do?",
        "answers": [
          {
            "answer" : "Purchase a Property.",
            "value" : 0
          }
        ],
    "sub-questions" : [
      {
        "question": "Which property would you like to buy?",
        "answers": [
          "TO BE PROGRAMMATICALLY UPDATED"
        ]
      }
      ]
    }
    ],
  "fireDamageProperty" : [
    {
    "question": "Player Must Burn an oil rig. Which property",
        "answers": [
           "TO BE PROGRAMMATICALLY UPDATED"
        ],
       "sub-questions" : [
    ]
      }
    ],
  "drillForFirstOil" : [
    {
    "question": "Player must drill for oil. Which property would you like to drill on?",
        "answers": [
        ],
       "sub-questions" : [
    ]
      }
    ],
  "drillForOil" : [
    {
    "question": "Player can drill for oil. Which property would you like to drill on?",
        "answers": [
          {
              "answer": "Stop drilling for oil.",
              "value": -2
          }
        ],
       "sub-questions" : [
    ]
      }
    ]
}
